<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Help on</title><link>https://matrix-python.github.io/docs/help/</link><description>Recent content in Help on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matrix-python.github.io/docs/help/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to update Element</title><link>https://matrix-python.github.io/docs/help/how-to-update/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 13:26:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://matrix-python.github.io/docs/help/how-to-update/</guid><description>If you are using the element-web on https://app.element.io/ or any web based version of Element, you are good to go. You don&amp;rsquo;t need to update anything manually. When there is a new version available, Element will notify you. Then you have get the option to switch to the new one.
If you are using element-desktop (The desktop version), you may have to update Element on your own.
If you are using the App on your smartdevice, you have to update manually.</description></item><item><title>Troubleshooting</title><link>https://matrix-python.github.io/docs/help/troubleshooting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 15:22:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://matrix-python.github.io/docs/help/troubleshooting/</guid><description>Unable to join the community Space? You can only join the Space with a compatible client and homeserver. Since Spaces are a brand-new feature, only the newest versions of the Element client are supporting them. Same with the homeservers Synapse and Dendrite.
If you are using older versions or different clients, you are currently not able to join the Space. Nevertheless, you can join the rooms manually. You will find the room IDs in Quick Start →</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://matrix-python.github.io/docs/help/faq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://matrix-python.github.io/docs/help/faq/</guid><description>Q: How can I report issues? ⚠
If the issue is website related, please follow our guide on how to create an issue on GitHub.
If you experience or witness unacceptable behaviour — or have any other concerns — please report it by contacting us via email abuse@MichaelSasser.org or in Matrix: Name Matrix Matrix Identifier BrenBarn BrenBarn @brenbarn:matrix.</description></item></channel></rss>